声明：本字幕由YYeTs人人影视字幕组原创翻译制作
禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
欢迎登录人人影视论坛交流 下载 在线观看 www.YYeTs.net
■
=====本字幕由以下成员荣誉制作 感谢他们的无私奉献======
翻译：66 亚历9大 paradise
校对：美景时间轴：YY吕伟 leolou
========== 字幕总监制：何何   ==========
前面会有些风变
We got a little chop ahead.
拿开那个  不要吓唬我
Put that away, man. you're freaking me out.
我们需要这个东西
We need this thing.
我们载的这些人?
With the cargo we got back there?
太不吉利
Bad mojo.
-Decker小姐?  -什么事?
Ms. decker? yes?
-想通知下后面我们要着陆了吗?  -好的
Wanna head back there and let 'em know we're landing? sure. of course.
我们要着陆了
We're coming in for a landing.
是在檀香山西部的一个军事基地
It's a military facility just west of honolulu.
是绝对机密的一个地方
It's completely private.
你们的--你们的家人已经来了
Your--your families are already here.
现在有很多新闻媒体想要采访你们
Now there's a lot of press that wanna speak to you,
但是据我所知大洋航空也关心说
But as far as oceanic is concerned,
你们不必接受记着的访问
You don't have to speak to any reporters.
我们可以接受访问
We'll talk to 'em.
你们也同意吗?
Is that all right with all of you?
没关系  我们都同意了
It's fine. we all agreed.
我们只是--只是想快点结束
We just--we just wanna get it over with.
好的
Okay.
他们把你们叫做"大洋航班六人"
Um, they're referring to you as the "oceanic six."
这个名字不是特别好  不过容易记
That's not the best branding as far as we're concerned, but it's catchy.
我们地面上见
We'll see you on the ground.
我们都知道要怎么说了
We all know the story.
如果我们遇到一些不想回答的
If we get any questions that we don't wanna answer,
或者不能回答的问题  我们就不回答
Or that we can't answer, let's just keep our mouths shut.
没什么的  他们会...以为我们还惊魂未定
It's okay. they'll--they'll think that we're in shock.
我们确实还惊魂未定呢  Jack
We are in shock, jack.
那样就应该很容易忽悠过去了
Then this should be easy.
是Sayid和Desmond在直升机上  对吗?
It was sayid and--and desmond in the helicopter, right?
我是说  一定是他们
I mean, it had to be.
不然他们为什么把这个东西正好扔给我们?
Why else would they have dropped that thingamabob right over us?
那他们为什么不干脆在这着陆呢?
Then why wouldn't they just land?
我不知道  不过这个东西可以追踪直升机
I don't know, but this thing is trackin' the chopper.
所以如果是他们  他们是想我们知道他们的去向
So if they were on it, they want us to know where they're going.
那是个电话  对吗?  为什么不直接打过去?
It's a phone, right? can't we just call?
别耍花招
Don't try anything stupid.
明白
Understood.
-在那着陆  -是从直升机上传出来的吗?
Put it down over there. is that from the chopper?
-我们离目的地还有五公里  -我叫你着陆  Frank
We're still 5 klicks from the site. I said put it down, frank.
动作快点  伙计们
Okay, gear up, boys.
我们一着陆  即刻前往"兰花站"
Soon as we hit the ground, we deploy to the orchid.
加油  行动吧
Heads down! let's do this.
你知道什么是"兰花站"吗?
You know what "the orchid" is?
不知道  我没听见Desmond和Sayid的声音
No. I didn't hear desmond or sayid either.
Kate
Kate.
-想走走吗?  -没问题
Wanna take a walk? absolutely.
-我去拿枪  你去取点水  好吗?  -好的
I'll get the guns. you get some water, okay? okay.
你在开玩笑吧  你刚动完手术  Jack
You can't possibly be serious. you just had surgery, jack.
-我没事的  -如果你的缝合处裂开  那就难办了
I'm gonna be fine. if your sutures rip, you're not gonna be fine.
-我不能只干坐在那等着  -是恢复不是"干坐着"!
I can't just sit around waiting. recovery is not "sitting around"!
-听着　我一定要去  -为什么?
Look, I have to do this. why?
因为我承诺过会带他们离开这个岛的
Because I promised those people that I would get 'em off this island.
别流血过多至死  Jack
Don't bleed to death, jack.
我们几个小时后见
I'll see ya in a couple hours.
-怎么了?  -Charlotte  你没听到他说什么吗?
What's wrong? charlotte, did you hear what he said?
他们要去兰花站
They're going to the orchid.
-他们在执行第二方案  -你说什么?
They're using the secondary protocol. what are you talking about?
兰花站
The Orchid
我们必须得离开这个岛
We have to get off this island.
马上
Right now.
我们快赶上了
We're catchin' up.
直升机肯定已经着陆了
The chopper must've landed.
你干嘛不歇口气?
Why don't you take a break?
你在流血
You're bleeding.
不  我不是在流血  我是...
No, I'm not bleeding. I'm...
是在化脓  是...
I'm suppurating. it's...
流脓  我的身体正和伤口处的感染做斗争
Discharge. my body's just fightin' the infection around the stitches.
大多数人撒谎时是不敢正视别人眼睛的
You know when most people are lying and they can't look you in the eye?
你却完全相反
You do the exact opposite.
好久不见
Hey, long time no see.
成吉思汗  你在和谁说话?
Hey, who are you talkin' to up there, genghis?
Claire在哪?
Where's claire?
我们把她弄丢了
We lost her.
你什么?
You what?
她半夜的时候走了
She just walked off in the middle of the night.
我们找了她一天  不过找不到
We looked for her for a day, but she was just gone.
-我希望她也许回到海滩那里了  -她没有
I was hopin' maybe she went back to the beach. she didn't.
你们在这干什么?
Well, what are y'all doin' out here?
那个电话是干什么的?
What's that phone for?
直升机飞过了海滩  有人把这个扔下来了
The chopper flew over the beach. someone tossed this out.
肯定是Sayid
It must've been sayid.
你最好希望不是Sayid
Well, you better hope it ain't sayid,
因为如果他和那帮炸毁了一半"其他人"的基地的混蛋在一起
'cause if he's with those animals that just blew up half of new otherton,
-你就不用指望可以救他了  -什么  他们要杀你们?
You do not wanna tussle with 'em. what, they tried to kill you?
就像Locke说的  他们会的
Just like locke said they would.
那么...怎么样?
So... what?
我们就干脆...掉头回去然后躲起来?
We're supposed to just... turn around and hide?
因为似乎你已经被找到了
'cause it seems like that didn't work so well for you.
抱歉  医生  可能这是不怎么样
I'm sorry, doc, maybe this is daijobu.
可是你的"拿着对讲机在丛林里乱晃"的办法也不怎么好
But didn't you just do the whole "run through the jungle with a walkie" plan?
那个直升机是我们离开这个岛的唯一办法
That helicopter is our only way off this island.
你为什么这么执着要"离开这个岛"?
What's with you and "gettin' off the island"?
-天天TMD想着这件事  -别说了!
You're like a damn broken record. stop it!
你们俩现在是要打架啊?
Are you two fightin' each other now?
我让Sayid和Desmond去直升机上的
I put sayid and desmond on that chopper.
是我的决定  所以是我的责任
It was my call. it's my responsibility.
无论他们在不在那我都要去看看
I'm going after it whether they're on it or not.
你们都可以回去海滩那
You can all head back to the beach.
Jack...  不不不  你不能自己一个人去
Jack... no, no, no. you can't go by yourself.
照顾好小婴儿  好吗?
Take care of the baby. okay?
那个狗娘养的太固执了
That son of a bitch is stubborn.
等等!  别想自己去送死
Hold up! you don't get to die alone.
基于对遇难位置的分析
Based on the location of the wreckage,
最有可能的失事地点是...
Our best estimate of the crash site is...
这里  从那里  幸存者们被洋流带到了...
Here. from there, the survivors were carried by the ocean's current to...
这里  巽他群岛里一个叫做Membata的无人小岛
Here-- an uninhabited island in the lesser sunda islands known as membata.
在你们的摘要手册里有  在第103天
As you've all read in your briefing books, on day 103...
一场台风把一艘印尼的渔船残骸吹到了岛上
A typhoon washed up the remnants of an indonesian fishing boat,
包括基本的供给和一条救生筏
Including basic supplies and a survival raft.
第108天  剩下的六名幸存者  包括
On day 108, the remaining six survivors, including
Austen小姐在Membata岛上生下的孩子
Ms.Austen's baby which she gave birth to on the island of membata,
划着救生筏到了这里  一个叫做Sumba的岛
Used this raft to journey here-- an island called sumba.
他们然后在一个叫做Manukangga的村落附近上岸
They then came ashore near a village called manukangga.
这张照片是当地渔民找到他们时拍下的
This photo was taken by the local fisherman who found them.
查明他们身份之后
Once it was discovered who they were,
他们就马上被美国海岸警卫队转移到了檀香山
They were transported to honolulu by the u.s. coast guard.
你们都能想象得出  这是一次非凡的求生经历
As you can imagine, this has been an extraordinarily trying experience.
他们同意回答一些问题
They have, however, agreed to answer a few questions.
女生们先生们  有请大洋航班8-1-5的幸存者
So, ladies and gentlemen, the survivors of oceanic 8-1-5.
Shephard医生!  Shephard医生!
Yes. dr. shephard! dr. shephard!
你能回想一下飞机坠海那时的感受吗?
Can you tell us what it was like when the plane hit the ocean?
你是如何幸存下来的
Uh, how you survived.
一切  一切都发生得太快了
It--it all happened really fast.
我还记得当时刹那的冲击
I remember the impact.
我还记得飞机  慢慢地渗入海水
I remember the--the plane filling up with water.
我们几个跑到了逃生门那里  然后
A group of us got to the emergency door, and, um...
在沉下去之前逃了出去
Got out before it went down.
你们这些幸存下来的人  你们是游到岛上的吗?
And those of you who survived-- you swam to the island?
不是
No.
我们知道了垫子
We had, uh, cushions.
还有一些救生衣
We had some life jackets.
我们在水里快一天  然后洋流把我们带走了
We were in the water for over a day before the current took us in.
那时  只有我们八个人存活下来
By then, there was only eight of us left.
其他三个人呢
what happened to other three?
其中一个  他叫本·卡·莱尔
one of them, his name is boon ky lair
严重内伤  坠机三天后死亡
suffered tremendous internal injurys and died three days after the crash
一名女性  利维  第一周就去世了
a woman, livi, she didn't make through the first week,
查理·佩斯  我们离开前几周溺水身亡
charlie pace, he drown a few weeks before we were able to leave
Reyes先生
Mr.Reye
在你"死亡"之前...  你有超过1亿5千万的身价
you were worth more than $150 million at the time of your... death.
现在可以把钱都拿回来  你是什么感觉?
How does it feel to know you're going to get all that money back?
我根本不想要  一个子都不想要
I don't want it back, any of it.
那钱真是厄运
That money was bad luck.
-她说什么?  -有人给翻译下吗?
What did she say? can somebody translate that?
她问我丈夫是否是在岛上死亡的人之一
She asked if my husband was one of the people who died on the island.
不是
The answer is no.
他在飞机坠海的时候就身亡了
He never made it off the plane.
你知道伊拉克现在的情况吗
Are you aware of the situation iraq
有回去的打算吗
Do you have any plans to return?
那里没有值得我留恋的
There is nothing for me in iraq
夏普德先生  你回家了  有什么计划
and Mr.shephard, now that you are home,
what about your plans
我真的还没有考虑这个问题
I havent really thought too much about it.
我父亲在悉尼去世
My father died in sydney
坠机时我正带他回家
I was bringing him home for the funeral when the plan crashed
现在他的遗体还
even though the body is...
我想让他安息
I'd like to put him in rest
Austen小姐...
Ms. austen...
在岛上生孩子是什么感觉?
What was it like giving birth on the island?
很恐怖
Scary.
你的儿子  Aaron?
Your son--uh, aaron?
他现在多大了?
How old is he now?
他只有五周多一点
He's just a little over 5 weeks.
那么当美国司法部
So that would've made you about six months pregnant when the u.s.
在澳大利亚因为一宗谋杀案逮捕你时
Marshal service apprehended you in australia
你已经有六个月身孕  对吗?
For an outstanding murder warrant. is that correct?
Austen小姐的法律事宜  无可奉告
Uh, I'm afraid ms. austen's legal issue is off the table.
下一个问题
Next question.
Jarrah先生  考虑到你们6位幸存者
Mr. jarrah, given the amazing circumstances
竟然奇迹的生存下来  你认为
Surrounding the survival of you six, is it possible
有没有可能还有幸存者
There are any other survivors from the crash
没有被发现
Yet to be discovered?
没有  绝对没有
No. absolutely not.
你刚刚做得很好
You did good.
Jarrah先生
Mr. jarrah?
外面有位女士
There's a woman outside.
她说她认识你  但是她却不在亲属名单中
She says she knows you, but she wasn't on the list of family members.
她的名字叫Anoor Abed Jaseem
Her name is anoor abed jaseem.
Nadia?
Nadia
Nadia.
嘿!  这边
Hey! over here!
Sayid!  Desmond在哪儿
Sayid! where's desmond?
他很好  他在货轮上
He's fine. he's on the freighter.
听着  我准备要开始带人回去  一次6个
Listen, I'm going to start taking people back-- six at a time.
在直升机回到船上之前  我们必须得离开
We have to go right now before the helicopter gets back to the boat.
为什么我们要赶在直升机回去之前?
Why do we have to go to the boat before the chopper gets back?
飞机上的人打算杀了我们全部人
Because the men on that helicopter have every intention of killing us all.
-什么  -Jack和Kate才跟着它而去
What? jack and kate just went running after it.
什么时候才有人告诉我我们这是去哪儿
So when is someone gonna tell me where we're going?
我们要去一个叫兰花站的地方  Hugo
We're going to a place called the orchid, hugo.
那是哪里
And what's that?
是一个温室
It's a greenhouse.
我们为什么要去一个温室
And why are we going to a greenhouse exactly?
你听到John说的  我们准备去移动这个岛
You heard john. we're going to move the island.
对  那我们该怎么做
Right. and how are we gonna do that?
得小心翼翼
Very carefully.
如果你可以随心所欲的移动这个岛
Well, if you could move the island whenever you wanted,
为什么不在那些带着枪的疯子来之前就移动
Why didn't you just move it before the psychos with guns got here?
因为移动岛既危险又无法预料后果
Because doing it is both dangerous and unpredictable.
这是最后一招
It's a measure of last resort.
很好
Awesome.
让我来
Allow me.
镜子给我好吗
May I have that mirror, please?
你知道  这些已经放了15年了
You know, those are 15 years old.
-兄弟  你在干什么  -传信号
What are you doing, dude? communicating.
跟谁传信号
Communicating with who?
你觉得呢
Who do you think?
好了  现在我们可以走了
All right. now we can go.
等等  那是什么  你跟他们说什么了
Wait. what was that? what did you tell them?
不关你的事  John
None of your business, john.
Sayid  听着
Hey, sayid, listen.
如果你想去丛林找那架直升机
If you wanna run off into the jungle after the chopper,
-但是同时我们得让这些人离开这个岛  -追上Jack和Kate
But in the meantime, we need to get these people off this island. I won't be long.
-不需要太久的  -我现在就可以开始运送人员了
If I can catch up with jack and kate-- I can start ferrying people now.
我能安全转移他们
I can get them there safely.
在你回来的时候  我能把大部分人都转移到船上
By the time you get back, I can have most of these people on our boat.
我相信你知道船的方位  你最好现在开始
I trust you know the bearing. you'd better get going.
好的  第一组到救生艇上  6个人
All right, first group in the raft. we can fit six.
好的  等等
Okay, okay, hold on.
Sun怀孕了  你先走
Sun is pregnant. you should go first.
Sayid?
你在这里做什么
What are you doing here?
Jack以为你...  我知道他想什么呢
Jack thought that you-- I know what he thought.
-所以我要去找他  他走了多远了  -我不知道
That's why I'm going after him. how far ahead is he? I don't know.
他...他跟Sawyer在一起  大概一小时前我离开了他们
He's--he's with sawyer. I left them about an hour ago.
Jack有卫星电话  他们朝直升机走去了
Jack's got a sat-phone, and they're headed for the helicopter.
我能追踪他们
I can track them.
除非我跟你一起  要不你追不上他们
Look, you are not gonna catch up to them unless I go with you.
我们走吧
Let's go.
好的
Okay.
Claire在哪里
Where's claire?
把Aaron抱上船
Get aaron on the boat, okay? what?
没事的  回头见
It's all right. just... I'll see you there.
注意他的安全
Just keep him safe!
好的  这是第一组  我们走
All right, this is just the first trip. here we go.
我说过我要带你离开这个岛
i told you i'd get you off the island.
怎么会发生这种事
how could this happen.
这个人  先生...
whoever did it，sir...
用了5个不同的银行账户
...used five different banks.
叫Yoon马上过来!
Get Yoon up here right now!
现在!
now!
爸爸
Hello，Father
希望我没打扰到你们
I hope I'm not interrupting
没有  只是生意上的事情
No...It's just business.
生意上出问题了吗
Is something wrong?
公司里有一些麻烦
Just some complications with the company
你不明白的
Nothing you'd understand
肚子里的孩子怎么样了
How is the pregnancy?
不要假装关心我的孩子
Don't pretend to be interested in my baby.
我们都明白你不喜欢我的丈夫
We both know you hated my husband.
你说什么
What did you say?
你听到的
You hear me.
你讨厌Jin
You hated Jin.
你认为你是谁
What do you think you are.
我是你的父亲
I'm your father.
你要尊重我!
You will respect me!
大洋航班因为空难对我们进行了赔偿
Oceanic paid us out settlement for the crash.
赔偿金有好多零
It was very significant.
今早  我买下了这个公司的多数股权
This morning,i bought a controlling interest in your company.
所以现在你  得尊重我
So you now will respect me.
为什么...  你为什么要这样做
Why...would you do this?
你让我丈夫送了命
You ruined my husband's life.
因为你  我们才坐上那架飞机
It is because of you we were on that plane
有两个人得为他的死负责
Two people are responsible for his death.
你就是其中之一
You are one of them.
我快生孩子了
I am going to have my baby.
过后我们再谈关于这间公司未来的计划
And then we shall discuss the plans for the future of the company.
我们的公司
our company.
Tron先生?
Mr. tron?
Tron太太?
Lady tron?
我为什么要这样做
Why am I doing this?
惊喜一下!
Surprise!
生日快乐!  生日快乐!
Happy birthday! happy birthday!
生日快乐  Hugo!
Happy birthday, hugo!
你拿那个干什么
Hugo, what are you doing with that?
不知道  我以为可能有小偷或是什么的
I don't know. I thought there might be a prowler or something.
耶稣可不是武器
Jesus christ is not a weapon.
好了
Okay.
享受你的派对吧
Enjoy your party.
生日快乐  Hurley
Happy birthday, hurley.
嘿  Kate
Hey, kate. hey.
嗨  小家伙  说你好
Hey, little buddy. say hi.
Jack要晚到  不好意思
Jack's running late. sorry.
生日快乐  Hugo
Happy birthday, hugo.
哇  你们在这
Wow, you guys are here.
派对主题选得很有趣
Interesting choice of theme.
我妈...不太理解我们的感受(又回到岛上了  哈哈)
Yeah, my mom... really doesn't get it, dude.
大家都怎么样啊
Hey! how's everybody doing?
你们在谈什么
What are you talking about?
生火或是猎杀野猪?
Building a fire or huntin' boars?
我猜不是
I guess not.
你们介意我们失陪一会儿吗
Uh, listen. uh, do you mind, uh, excusing us for a little while?
给你看看我为你准备的生日礼物
I-i wanna show you your birthday present. hmm?
来吧  再见
Come on. bye-bye now.
我跟你说过我什么都不想要
I told you I don't want anything.
Hugo  这是你的生日  你一定要得到点什么
Hugo, it's your birthday. you gotta get somethin'.
不要和那些钱有关  我不想得到任何用那些钱买来的东西
Not with the money. I don't want anything from the money.
放松  在你给我们那些钱之前我就准备好了
Relax. I got this before you gave us the money.
看看
Check it out.
你把它修好了
You fixed it.
对
Yeah.
空难之后  我修好它做为对你的怀念
After the crash, i-i worked on it as a memorial to you.
当我修它时  就好像我跟你在一起一样
When I was fixing it up, it was almost like I was with ya.
现在你回来了  这是你的了
But now you're back, and it's all yours.
想开出去兜兜风吗
Wanna take her for a little spin?
-有什么问题吗  儿子?  -这是个玩笑吗
Is somethin' wrong, son? is this some kind of joke?
你在说什么
What are you talking about?
4  8  15  16  23  42
4, 8, 15, 16, 23, 42.
你做的这些吗?
Did you do this?
-做什么啊?  -这就是那个号码!
Do what? those are the numbers!
就这个  我彩票的中奖号码
Right there! the numbers I won the lottery with!
-哇  真是个巧合  -不  不  这不是巧合
Wow. what--what a coincidence. no. no, not a coincidence.
我不想要这个
I don't want this.
-我不想要这个  -Hugo?
I don't want any of it! hugo?
等等  Hugo  你要...
Wait--wait a minute. hugo, what are you...
儿子!
Son! hey!
Hugo!  Hugo!
Hugo! hugo!
你要去哪儿  Hugo
Hugo, where you goin'? come on! hugo!
好的  假设这个温室像你说的一样
Okay, let's say this greenhouse place does what you say, and, yeah,
既危险又不知道后果会怎样
I get it. it's really dangerous and unpredictable.
如果它起作用了  我们移动了这个岛
But suppose somehow it works, and we move the island.
是不是这就意味着那些带着枪的家伙也跟着移动
Doesn't that mean the dudes with guns move, too?
是的  我想他们也会跟着移动  这不就是个问题吗?
Yes, I suppose they would. well, isn't that, you know, a problem?
我正在想办法
I'm working on it.
那我怎么办  我还是想离开这个岛!
Well, what about me? I still wanna get off it!
恐怕现在有点迟了  Hugo
I'm afraid it's a little late for that, hugo.
把望远镜给我好吗
May I have the binoculars, please?
你们最好蹲低一点
You might wanna get down lower to the ground.
为什么我们要那样做
And why might we wanna do that?
因为我们已经到兰花站了
Because we're at the orchid.
那我们还等什么?
What are we waitin' for?
我们之所以等  是因为Charles Widmore
We're waiting, john, because charles widmore,
那个想要抓住我  然后把你们都杀掉的人
The man who's trying to capture me and kill all the rest of you,
他知道这个地方  知道里面有我们要的东西
Knows about this place and knows that what we need is inside.
你曾说过你不知道他为何想要找到这岛
I thought you said you had no idea why he was trying to find he island.
我当时说的不全是真话
I wasn't being entirely truthful.
是啊  你什么时候会全说真话呢
Yeah. when are you ever entirely truthful?
你得看看这个
You need to see this.
你要我看什么?
What am I looking for?
往左手边看
Look over there on the left-hand side.
朝后面植物的方向看
Watch the plants at the back.
-我没有看到任何...  -他们已经来了
I don't see any-- they're already here.
我们回来了
Hey, we're back!
Sayid呢?
Where's sayid?
他去追Jack了  你上
He had to go after jack. you go.
他们去追直升机了
They're headed for the chopper.
你还好吗?
You okay?
是的  我很好  谢谢
Yes, I'm fine. thank you.
我回去接下一批人
I'm gonna head back for the next group.
发动机修好了
Engine's fixed.
去叫Hendricks来试一下
Tell hendricks to try it.
好了  发动机应该能用了
Okay, engine should be working.
的确如此
Indeed they are.
好了  朝岛那边开
All right, well, take us to the island.
但你得确保是在3-0-5的方位开去
But make sure you--you stay on the bearing of 3-0-5.
必须得在3-0-5方位上
It's gotta be exactly 3-0-5.
看来有射频干扰回声测深仪
We've got some kind of r.f. interference with the the fathometer.
我看不到暗礁了  老兄
I can't see the reef, mate.
射频干扰吗
R.f. interference?
怎么可能?  无线电已经出故障了
How is that possible? the radio room's down.
我不清楚  但是船上有什么东西在传送信号
I don't know, but something on this boat is broadcasting.
如果不把它关上
If we don't turn it off,
我不会进入岛的5英里范围
I'm not going any closer than 5 miles off the coast.
那我去把它找出来
Then I'll find it.
刮胡子伤到的吗
Cut yourself shavin'?
两天前Juliet切了我的阑尾
Juliet took out my appendix a couple of days ago.
你耍我吧
You kiddin' me.
没有
Nope.
我还错过了什么呢?
Well, what else did I miss?
我们到了
We're here.
是Lapidus吗
Ah! lapidus!
是
Yeah!
你认识这混蛋吗
You know this yahoo?
是的
Yeah.
混蛋?
"yahoo"?
是我这个混蛋把电话丢出去  好让你们找到我...
This yahoo dropped that phone on you guys so you could find me...
然后带你们离开这里
And I could fly you outta here.
因此你为何不帮我一下?
So why don't you do me a favor and get that back compartment?
在后舱里有个工具箱
There's a toolbox.
看是否能找到有用的东西把我从这鬼东西弄出来
See if you can find something to get me outta these things.
照做吧
You heard the man.
我回来时要不要给你们带一杯可口的冰柠檬汁?
Can I get you boys a nice, cold glass of lemonade while I'm back there?
Desmond和Sayid在哪
Where are desmond and sayid?
你们的朋友很聪明  继续呆在船上
Your buddies were smart enough to keep their asses on
因为就目前而言船上是最安全的地方
The boat because right now that's the safest place to be.
因为我带回来的那帮人
Because when the boys that I brought over here come
走进这丛林  你们会希望离的远远滴
Stomping' out of this jungle, you're gonna wanna be long gone.
他们去哪里了?
Where'd they go?
他们朝温室去了  驻扎在那边  就等Linus落网
They're up by some greenhouse, perched up there, waitin' to snatch linus.
只要我们把你弄出来  你就能带我们离开这里吗
Soon as we cut you free, you'll be able fly us out of here?
-是的  -等等  混蛋
Hell, yeah. hang on, shaggy.
你说那帮人要抓Ben Linus?
You said the hit squad's gonna grab ben linus?
我想不到他们不抓他的理由
Well, I don't see what's gonna stop 'em.
他们要怎么处置和他一起的人?
What are they gonna do with the people that are with 'em?
反正不会善待
Nothin' good.
Hugo和Ben在一起
Hugo's with ben.
见鬼!
Son of a bitch.
大约在十个月前
About ten months ago,
我就写好了我父亲葬礼的悼言
I wrote what I wanted to say at my father's funeral
在悉尼机场时我把它写在了鸡尾酒餐巾上
On the back of a cocktail napkin at the sydney airport.
我记不清我写的什么了  但是那个内容
I don't remember what I wrote, but whatever it was...
我保证他不会喜欢
He would've hated it.
我父亲不喜欢被人赞颂
My father couldn't stand eulogies.
他曾说"清醒的唯一好处就是又可以大醉一场"
"the only good thing about a wake is the free booze," he'd say.
根本就没有守灵(双语)  因为我连葬送他的机会都没有
Not much of a wake because I won't even be able to bury him.
因此...
So...
我说的这些不是说给我父亲听的
What I wanna say is not for my father.
是说给我自己听的
It's for me.
一路好走  爸爸
Good-bye, dad.
我爱你
I loved you.
我想念你
I miss you.
非常感谢你的到来  谢谢  谢谢
Thanks very much for coming. thank you. thank you.
非常感谢你的到来  谢谢
Thank you for coming. thanks.
-一会回家见?  -好的
I'll see you back at the house? yeah.
-我爱你  亲爱的  -我爱你  妈妈
I love you, sweetheart. I love you, mom.
我很高兴你回来了
I'm so glad you're home.
-呆会儿见  -好的
I'll see you soon. okay.
你做得很好
You did that well.
练了很多次
Had a lot of practice.
打扰一下
Excuse me.
我能和你说几句话吗
May I have a word with you?
Shephard先生...
Mr. shephard...
你失去了父亲  我感到很遗憾
I'm very sorry for your loss.
谢谢
Thank you.
你怎么会认识我父亲?
How did you know my father?
我想他来澳大利亚的原因是因为我
I believe I'm the reason he was in australia when he died.
抱歉  我不明白你的意思
I'm sorry. I don't understand.
他为什么要跑去看你?
Why would he have come to see you?
他...他不是来看我
Oh, he... he didn't come to see me.
那时我还在医院  我们没见到面
I was still in the hospital. I never saw him.
他是来看他的女儿
He came to see his daughter.
也是我的女儿  Shephard先生
My daughter, mr. shephard.
-我父亲不曾有过女儿  -不  他有
My father didn't have a daughter-- yes. he did.
如果你不相信我  你可以去查一下电话记录
If you don't believe me, check his phone records.
还有更奇怪的事  你想知道吗?
Would you like to know the--the strangest thing about all this,
我的女儿也在你们的飞机上
My daughter was on your plane, too.
她也在815航班上
She was on flight 8-1-5.
你们在飞机上呆了6个小时  你可能就在她的前几排
You were in the air for six hours, probably just a few rows from her.
而你却不知道她是你妹妹
And you never even knew she was your sister.
你们的飞机坠海时  她就死了
She was one of the ones who died when your plane hit the water.
她的名字是...
Her name was...
Claire
Claire.
我不想再给你增加负担  但是...
I didn't mean to burden you with this, but...
你有必要知道这件事
You needed to know.
我...
I'm...
你失去亲人  我很抱歉
Sorry for your loss.
你儿子很漂亮
Your son is beautiful.
我不明白  你是怎样回到纽约的?
I don't understand. how'd you get back to new york?
我和Walt...
Uh, walt and i, uh, uh...
我们坐上Ben的船沿着轴向开回去的
We took ben's boat and we followed his bearing.
两天过后  我们到了一个有人居住的岛上
A couple of days, we came to an island, you know, with people.
然后我们搭乘一条货船回到美国
We hopped a cargo ferry back to the states.
不曾告诉别人我们的来历
Didn't tell anybody who we were.
现在你在为Ben卖命吗?
And now you're working for ben?
我没有为Ben卖命
I do not work for ben.
我努力弥补我的过失
I'm trying to make up for what I did.
我想帮你们离开那里
I'm trying to help you out here.
翻译我说的话
Translate what I said.
我听的懂
I understand.
嘿  michael!  快过来!
Hey! michael! I need you now!
天哪
Oh, my god.
什么情况?
What's the matter?
这不是Jack或Sawyer的脚印
These aren't jack or sawyer.
是其他人的  刚留下的...
They're different tracks, fresh...
他们绕到我们后面去了
And they're doubling back behind us.
不管你是谁  快给我滚出来!
Whoever you are, come out now!
好
All right.
好  放松
All right, let's just relax.
-好  放松  -停下来!  停下来!
All right, let's-- let's just rel--let's relax. stop! stop!
-放松  放下手枪  -我叫你停下来!
Just relax. put the guns down. pl-- I said stop right there!
-请你们放下枪  -你再走一步...  -我说过放下枪
Please just drop your guns. take one more step-- I said drop your guns.
我看见其中两个  但没有杀死Alex的那个人
I see two of them, but not the one who killed alex.
他在那
He's there.
帮我拿着这个  好吗
Hold on to that for me, will you?
什么?
What?
仔细听我说  John
Listen to me very carefully, john,
因为我没时间重复
Because I'm not gonna have time to repeat this.
你得穿过那个洞进去温室
You're gonna go into that greenhouse through that hole there.
一旦进去  左转
Once inside, you're gonna turn left.
大约走20步  直到在左手边看到一片花烛为止
Go about 20 paces until you see a patch of anthuriums on your left.
他们在壁凹里背对北墙
They're in an alcove against the north wall.
面对墙壁  用左手伸进去
Face that wall, reach down with your left hand.
你会摸到开升降机的开关
You'll find a switch that activates the elevator.
升降机会带你们到兰花站台
The elevator takes you down to the actual orchid station.
等等 什么?
Whoa. wait. What?
好的  抱歉  Ben
Okay, I'm sorry, ben
你恐怕得解释一下
But maybe I missed the part where you explained
我要怎样对付里面那些武装人员
what I'm supposed to do about the armed men inside.
我去应付他们
I'm gonna take care of them.
你他妈要怎样去应付他们
And how the hell are you gonna do that?
我跟你说过多少次了  John?
How many times do I have to tell you, john?
我自有办法
I always have a plan.
Ben!
我是Benjamin Linus
My name is benjamin linus.
我想你们正在找我吧
I believe you're looking for me.
==============| YYeTs字幕组招募启示 |==============
英文字幕录制(居住在加拿大和美国) 双语字幕校正 时间轴调整
英语翻译 欧美影视新闻翻译 影视评论 论坛版主 美工人员
服务器提供者 发布宣传 联系地址：www.YYeTs.net
==== YYeTs属于网络爱好者组织 加入者仅凭个人兴趣爱好 无报酬 ====